inkfrog.com 2006-03-19

# InkFrog.com - eBay auction management and image hosting

At inkFrog, inc we care about providing you with tools and information to manage and protect your online privacy. We have developed this privacy policy to inform you about what information this web site collects, who may receive that information, what we may do with the information. While we have made every attempt to make this policy as clear as possible, if you have any further questions about it, please contact us: 

inkFrog, inc.  
P.O. Box 915  
Higley, Az 85236  
email: privacy@inkfrog.com  
Phone: 1-480-924-0594

Will this information be shared with third parties?

No, inkFrog, inc. will never share your personal information to third parties without written consent from you. Of course this will not limit the use, disclosure, or distribution of personally identifiable information to the extent that such use, disclosure, or distribution is required by law, court order, or other valid legal process. 

Does inkFrog, inc use cookies to keep track of my information?

Yes, inkfrog.com utilizes cookies in order to allow us to help track the user through the site and keep them logged in to their account for the session time. Users have the right to disable cookies or not accept cookies. Please note, that cookies are required to utilize inkFrog's services. We use cookies to monitor the site usage and to help improve the way the site works. We do not disclose any information obtained from cookies to any third party.

What types of information does inkFrog collect?  
Traditional contact information such as name, email address, mailing address, and phone number.  
Demographic information on registration forms, if you choose to provide it. This information helps us understand the needs of our users and to improve the site.  
Non-financial identification information, such as username and password combinations for use to login and track into our members area.  
User content on our forums (if you choose to post in the forums). Note that information posted on the user forums will be displayed publicly, and will not be governed by this privacy policy.  
Credit cards are collected for 'auto pay' if users choose to use this option. The information from these cards are taken over a secure connection (ssl) and encrypted before being stored in our database for security.   
inkFrog uses 128 bit encryption technology to protect sensitive information such as password and credit card data.

Log Files:  
inkFrog tracks Information about the user's computer system, such as the web browser type, IP address, and operating system. This is used for logging purposes only and used to improve the inkFrog site. 

Why do we collect this information?:   
For website administration purposes.   
To evaluate, review, or improve the website.   
To customize the website for the user on multiple visits to the site.   
To notify members of updates to the sites, and/or contact them to market products or services. Members will not be contacted for marketing purposes unless they "opt-in" to receive this information.

We do not supplement Personally identifiable information collected on the site with information from other sources.

inkFrog desires to maintain accurate information about you. You may review or change your personally identifiable information on webpages within our site at any time. After logging in, click the "account info" link, and click on "edit. If for some reason you cannot access these pages, you may send updates and corrections about your information to our customer support department at http://www.inkfrog.com/index.php?file=support.

Changes to this policy:

You will be notified of any material change to this privacy policy or material change in the collection, use or disclosure of personally identifiable information prior to making the changes. We will a)post prominent notices on the site for 14 days prior to implementation of any change and b)send an administrative e-mail to all users affected by the change 14 days prior to implementation of any change, with a description of how you may exercise any applicable choice.

If you believe we are not handling your information in accordance with our privacy policy, please contact our customer service department. Contact information is available at http://www.inkfrog.com/index.php?file=support.

If for some reason we have violated our privacy policy, we will correct the error as soon as you notify us. 

The effective date of this privacy policy is March 1, 2005.
